<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-18T22:59:18+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">(mis)interpreting Hegel</title><subtitle>A blog dedicated into discussion of Hegel&apos;s works and wherever it can be applied to.</subtitle><author><name>Grigory Gil</name></author><entry><title type="html">banana</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/bananas/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="banana" /><published>2022-12-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/bananas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/bananas/">&lt;p&gt;A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds
of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In some countries, bananas used for cooking may be called “plantains”,
distinguishing them from dessert bananas. The fruit is variable in size, color,
and firmness, but is usually elongated and curved, with soft flesh rich in
starch covered with a rind, which may be green, yellow, red, purple, or brown
when ripe.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Grigory Gil</name></author><category term="fruit" /><summary type="html">A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">apple</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/apples/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="apple" /><published>2022-12-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/apples</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/apples/">&lt;p&gt;An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple trees are cultivated worldwide, and are the most widely grown species in
the genus Malus. The tree originated in Central Asia, where its wild ancestor,
Malus sieversii, is still found today. Apples have been grown for thousands of
years in Asia and Europe, and were brought to North America by European
colonists.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Grigory Gil</name></author><category term="fruit" /><summary type="html">An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">kiwi</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/kiwi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="kiwi" /><published>2022-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/kiwi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/kiwi/">&lt;p&gt;Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible
berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most common cultivar group of kiwifruit is oval, about the size of a large
hen’s egg (5–8 cm (2.0–3.1 in) in length and 4.5–5.5 cm (1.8–2.2 in) in
diameter). It has a fibrous, dull greenish-brown skin and bright green or
golden flesh with rows of tiny, black, edible seeds. The fruit has a soft
texture, with a sweet and unique flavor.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Grigory Gil</name></author><category term="fruit" /><summary type="html">Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.</summary></entry></feed>