<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-28T15:04:40+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">(mis)interpreting Hegel</title><subtitle>A blog dedicated into discussion of Hegel&apos;s works and wherever it can be applied to.</subtitle><author><name>Grigory Gil</name></author><entry><title type="html">sense-certainty</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sense-certainty/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="sense-certainty" /><published>2022-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sense-certainty</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sense-certainty/">&lt;p&gt;Within sense-certainty the existence of an object is self-justifiable, its being 
is only within it, or, in other words, there is no justification for its existence - but it keeps existing otherwise.
The truth of an object contains nothing other than its own being,
an object in sense-certainty does not have a narration of its appearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This pure-being / simple immediacy is what makes the object true.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The object exists as a This and has the forms of Now and Here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When sense-certainty tries to describe this object it does so through the universal - 
but by doing so it fails and manages to express the particular of the universal.
The universal presents the true content of itself 
while language presents the expression of the true content.
Language cannot identify being, only its expression.
But through the failure of identifying being using language, this failure happens in 
relation to what gave its failure, this happens in mediation to the universal.
A measure happens to what entices if its right or wrong and this happens with the 
help of the universals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to conclude:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The universal is always itself - it is immediate.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The particular is negated in relation to the universal - it is mediated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you describe an object, due to it being immediate, 
this immediacy disappears as a new one arises.
But this disappearance is what enables us, through mediation, to arrive 
at what was immediate. So the immediate upon capture - unmediates itself because 
this capture is what creates the situation in which the immediate vanishes, and out of 
this vanishing a new immediate appears in order for mediation to happen between the former and the present 
immediacies. Do note that by definition the former immediacy stops being itself.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Grigory Gil</name></author><category term="consciousness" /><summary type="html">Within sense-certainty the existence of an object is self-justifiable, its being is only within it, or, in other words, there is no justification for its existence - but it keeps existing otherwise. The truth of an object contains nothing other than its own being, an object in sense-certainty does not have a narration of its appearance.</summary></entry></feed>